二零二零年，怀化市初中毕业学业考试
exam, B, and 1.
英语听力第一节对话理解。
听下面五段对话，每段对话后。
有一个小题：从题中所给的
三个选项中选出最佳选项，并标在试卷的相应位置。
听完每段对话后，你将有十秒钟的时间来回答有关小题和阅读。
下一小题，每段对话读两遍。
Mary, what can you do?
I can play basketball.
2. What animals do you like,
I like pandas.
What animals do you like, Lucy?
3. Is Mike watching TV now?
Yes, he is.
Mike watching TV now?
4. What's the weather like today?
It's sunny. What's the weather like today?
It's sunny. 5.
How much are these socks?
They are seven dollars.
第二节，听下面五段对。
对话或独白，每段对话或独白后有几个小题。
从题中所给的
B, and sixth to seventh
三个选项中选出最佳选项，并标在试卷的相应位置。
听每段对话或独白前。
你将有时间阅读各个小题，
每小题五秒钟。
听完后，各小题将给出五秒钟的作答时间。
每段对话或独白读两遍。
听第六段材料，回答。
6. Excuse me, is this your school bag, Tom?
No, it isn't.
My school bag is blue.
Whose school bag is it?
It must be Sally's.
Her name is on it.
Excuse me, is this your school bag, Tom?
No, it isn't.
My school bag is blue.
Whose school bag is it?
It must be Sally's.
Her name is on it.
听第七段材料，回答第。
to ninth Good afternoon.
May I take your order?
Yes. Are there any vegetables in the beef noodles?
Yes. There are some tomatoes.
Okay. I'd like one bowl of beef noodles.
Sure. What size would you like?
Large, please. Okay.
Just wait for a minute.
Good afternoon. May I take your order?
Yes. Are there any vegetables in the beef noodles?
Yes. There are some tomatoes.
Okay. I'd like one bowl of beef noodles.
Sure. What size would you like?
Large, please. Okay.
Just wait for a Good morning, Ms.
听第八段材料，回答第十至十二题。
Good morning, Jack.
Is this your new bike?
Yes. I ride it to school every day.
How far is it from your home to school?
It's about five kilometers.
How long does it take you to get to school?
About fifteen minutes by bike.
It's good exercise.
Good morning, Is this your new bike?
Yes. I ride it to school every day.
How far is it from your home to school?
It's about five kilometers.
How long does it take you to get to school?
About fifteen minutes by bike.
It's good exercise.
Yeah. Well, have a nice day at school.
You too. I had a school trip last week.
听第九段材料，回答第十三至十六题。
Really? Where did you go?
I visited the museum.
Who did you go with?
I went with my classmates.
What did you do?
We saw a lot of robots.
Did you learn anything?
Sure. We learned how to make a modern robot.
I had a school trip last week.
Really? Where did you go?
I visited the museum.
Who did you go with?
I went with my classmates.
What did you do?
We saw a lot of robots.
Did you learn anything?
Sure. We learned how to make a modern robot.
听第十段材料，回答第十七至二十题。
I had trip My favorite subject is Chinese.
Our teachers are kind and helpful.
Whenever I have problems, they're always ready to give me a hand.
School activities are rich and colorful.
I often play basketball with classmates.
I like reading, and I want to be a writer in the future.
So I often spend my free time reading in the school library.
My school life is wonderful, and I enjoy it very much.
I'm Lihua from Sunny Middle School.
My school is across from a park.
I'd like to share my school life with you.
We have many subjects at school, such as Chinese, English, and so on.
My favorite subject is Chinese.
Our teachers are kind and helpful.
Whenever I have problems, they're always ready to give me a hand.
School activities are rich and colorful.
I often play basketball with classmates.
I like reading, and I want to be a writer in the future.
So I often spend my free time reading in the school library.
My school life is wonderful, and I enjoy it very much.
听力考试到此结束，请同学们继续做下面的试题。
监考老师，请关机。
Chinese, and Chinese,